Delivering justice, one shell at a time...
Hobo with a Shotgun is a crime, action, thriller film directed by Jason Eisener.
A vigilante homeless man pulls into a new city and finds himself trapped in urban
chaos, a city where crime rules and where the city's crime boss reigns.
Seeing an urban landscape filled with armed robbers, corrupt cops, abused prostitutes and even a pedophile Santa,
the Hobo goes about bringing justice to the city the best way he knows how - with a 20-gauge shotgun.
Mayhem ensues when he tries to make things better for the future generation.
Street justice will indeed prevail.
Hobo, played by Rutger Hauer.
Abby, played by Molly Dunsworth.
Slick, played by Gregory Smith.
Logan, played by Robb Wells.
The Drake, played by Brian Downey.
Ivan / Rip, played by Nick Bateman.
Hobo with a Shotgun is a 2011 exploitation black comedy action film
directed by Jason Eisener and written by John Davies.
Based on Eisener's fictitious trailer of the same name from Grindhouse (2007), it is the second feature-length
adaptation of a fictitious Grindhouse trailer, following Robert Rodriguez's Machete (2010).
Hobo with a Shotgun premiered at the Sundance Film Festival on January 21,
2011, on March 25 in Canada, and on May 6 in the United States.
The film received mixed reviews from critics and has become a cult film.
The film explores themes of prostitute, shotgun, dystopia, pimp, vigilante.
The tone is dark and intense.